export const generalQuestions = {
  data: [
    {
      index: 1,
      question: 'How do I submit a deal with you?',
      answer: 'You can submit a deal through https://traded.co/submit/.',
    },
    {
      index: 2,
      question: 'Who follows/posts on Traded?',
      answer:
        'Traded’s following consists of the top real estate professionals across the country including landlords, commercial & residential real estate brokers, lenders, tenants, bankers, developers, investors and more.',
    },
    {
      index: 3,
      question: 'What markets do you cover?',
      answer:
        'Our main markets are New York, Los Angeles, Miami, Boston, Chicago, Texas and New Jersey. We tend to cover deals in each of the states as well; for example, our Miami market covers deals in all of Florida.',
    },
    {
      index: 4,
      question: 'Will you be launching Traded for my city?',
      answer:
        'We tend to identify new feeds based on the commercial real estate activity in the market. If you think we should look into your city/region, email us at hello@traded.co.',
    },
    {
      index: 5,
      question: 'Where do the deals that get posted come from?',
      answer:
        'Deals come in a few different ways. They mainly come through submissions, but we also source deals from Traded’s in-house research team.',
    },
    {
      index: 6,
      question: "What is Traded's reach? Monthly Impressions?",
      answer:
        'Across all feeds and platforms (Instagram, LinkedIn, Twitter, Web, and Newsletter) we get about 20 MM impressions.',
    },
    {
      index: 7,
      question: 'Do you guys have a Newsletter?',
      answer:
        'Yes! You can subscribe by each city/state’s feed and if you would like to receive it daily or weekly. Visit https://traded.co/newsletters/ to subscribe!',
    },
    {
      index: 8,
      question: 'Does Traded have a phone number? Can I call you?',
      answer:
        'As of now we only chat via email, DM’s, and live chat on our website. Drop us a message, we are quick to respond!',
    },
    {
      index: 9,
      question: 'How much does it cost to submit a deal on Traded?',
      answer:
        'The costs vary based on the feed, price of the deal, deal type, and any additional features you would like to include with your post. Check our submission form here to see for yourself! Traded.co/submit',
    },
    {
      index: 10,
      question: 'What kind of transactions do you cover?',
      answer:
        'We mainly cover commercial real estate sales, loans and leases. In addition, we will cover high end residential and celebrity deals from time to time.',
    },
    {
      index: 11,
      question: 'What happens when my deal gets posted?',
      answer:
        'Once your deal is approved, Traded circulates your post to Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, Linkedin, Traded.co, and Pinterest.',
    },
    {
      index: 12,
      question: 'Is Traded Hiring?',
      answer:
        'Yes, we are always looking for people to join the Traded team. For job inquiries, please reach out directly to hello@Traded.co.',
    },
    {
      index: 13,
      question: 'How are the feeds structured?',
      answer:
        'Each market has it’s own feed and respective channels. Example: @TradedNY has an Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Pinterest and Reddit as well as @TradedLa and @TradedMia. In addition, all the deals are featured on our website Traded.co.',
    },
    {
      index: 14,
      question: 'Are the properties posted for sale/lease?',
      answer:
        'No. Traded is a media company, not a brokerage. We would suggest reaching out to a contact listed on our site!',
    },
    {
      index: 15,
      question: 'What is the goal of your website?',
      answer:
        'We are building out a publication, a data platform, and a marketplace for our users to learn, export data, showcase their listings, connect with others, and close more deals! We are currently building profiles of the agents & agencies. We will eventually release company profiles as well (inclusive of investors, banks/lenders) to showcase stats on the deals they did – where, when, how, and with who. We consider the website to be and interactive platform.',
    },
  ],
};

export const advertisingAndCollaborations = {
  data: [
    {
      index: 1,
      question: 'What are advertisements?',
      answer:
        'These are not submissions – it’s for people who want to post on our stories or banners on our website advertising something in particular. Generally if anyone wants to advertise with us above a transaction they want to feature, simple ask them to email ads@Traded.co.',
    },
    {
      index: 2,
      question: 'Can I advertise on Traded?',
      answer:
        'Please email us at ads@traded.co to get connected with our ad sales team.',
    },
    {
      index: 3,
      question: 'How can I contact your advertising department?',
      answer:
        'Please email us at ads@traded.co to get connected with our ad sales team.',
    },
    {
      index: 4,
      question: 'What are your advertising costs?',
      answer:
        'Please email us at ads@traded.co to get connected with our ad sales team.',
    },
    {
      index: 5,
      question: 'Can Traded boost my post for me?',
      answer:
        'Yes, we have an option for you to give us a budget and we will boost/advertise your deal to a targeted audience. Email us at hello@traded.co',
    },
    {
      index: 6,
      question: 'Can I post a general ad with Traded?',
      answer:
        'Yes, you can check out our Media Kit here! Email us at hello@Traded.co, and we will reach out to you.',
    },
    {
      index: 7,
      question: 'How can I find your advertising/media kit?',
      answer: 'You can find our media kit here.',
    },
    {
      index: 8,
      question: 'How can I create IGTV Content in partnership with Traded?',
      answer:
        'Please email us at ads@traded.co or dm us directly through instagram to discuss further.',
    },
    {
      index: 9,
      question: 'Can I promote my listing with you?',
      answer:
        'Not yet, although we are working towards including listings in a general advertising package.',
    },
  ],
};

export const submissions = {
  data: [
    {
      index: 1,
      question: 'How do I get featured on Traded?',
      answer:
        'Getting featured is easy. Submit the transaction details on Traded.co/submit, and our team will craft your image and get you posted ASAP. Please note, all posts are subject to an approval process (If Traded doesn’t approve the post, you will get a full refund).',
    },
    {
      index: 2,
      question: 'Can you remove a post once it is up?',
      answer:
        'In most cases, we are able to assist. Please email us at submit@traded.co or connect with us through our website chat box.',
    },
    {
      index: 3,
      question: 'Can I post a deal without Buyer & Seller name?',
      answer:
        'There is a fee to hide the name on NY, LA, Miami. The rest of the feeds are free. When you are submitting on the submission form it wont charge you when you choose the other feeds.',
    },
    {
      index: 4,
      question: 'Are package deals an option?',
      answer:
        'For package deals, please email ads@traded.co.',
    },
    {
      index: 5,
      question: 'Can I submit the deal without the address?',
      answer:
        'We require and adress with every submission for the purpose of creating the image. Once the image has been created and sent back for approval, you can request to hide the address for an additional fee.',
    },
    {
      index: 6,
      question:
        'My image is not uploading, how do I get it included in my submission?',
      answer:
        'If your image fails to upload, please feel free to email our submissions team at hello@Traded.co after you have submitted your deal; they will make sure those images get over to our editorial team along with your submission!',
    },
    {
      index: 7,
      question: 'Can you add my picture to a deal?',
      answer:
        'Please make sure once you approve your post, you are ready for it to go live! Once posted on our site and social the only way to edit the post is to remove and repost for a fee.',
    },
    {
      index: 8,
      question: 'Can you add a tag to a published post?',
      answer:
        'Yes. Please email us the usernames to be tagged at submit@traded.co or connect with us through our website chat box.',
    },
    {
      index: 9,
      question: 'Can I post a deal without a price?',
      answer:
        'We require the price to be featured in our feeds and website. The only exception is if your deal took place in Texas due to the state’s non-disclosure status.',
    },
    {
      index: 10,
      question: 'Can I edit my post once it is already published?',
      answer:
        'Once published, posts cannot be edited except for the caption and tags. If you need it to be redone, please email us at submit@traded.co. Bare in mind we charge a $250 repost fee.',
    },
    {
      index: 11,
      question: 'What happens when my deal gets posted?',
      answer: `Circulation: Once your deal gets posted, Traded circulates your post to our website where we will create a profile for you if you don’t already have one. Traded also posts it to its respective Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, Linkedin, Tumblr, and Pinterest pages.\n 

        Ranking: After your post gets circulated, your deal will likely rank on all major search engines, including Google and Bing for years to come to ensure you get the recognition you deserve and hopefully get you more business!\n
        
        Profile: We create a profile on our website including your deal, adding to your ranking & stats. `,
    },
    {
      index: 12,
      question: 'When can I expect my post to go live?',
      answer:
        'Posts can take anywhere from 3-7 days to go live due to the large amount of volume. If your post is time sensitive, please select “Speed Post” on our submission post. Your post will go live within 24 hours for a small fee.',
    },
    {
      index: 13,
      question: 'Will I see my post before it is published?',
      answer:
        'All submissions are sent for approval before we go live. You can have as many revisions as you like before we post!',
    },
    {
      index: 14,
      question: 'Can you remove and repost with a new image?',
      answer:
        'Once an image is posted on our site and social the only way to edit the post is to remove and repost for a fee.',
    },
    {
      index: 15,
      question: 'Can you post my deal next? Whats a speed post?',
      answer:
        'We have a lot of transactions coming in daily, and we post them in the order that we receive them. If you would like to have a rush post please choose the Speed Post option which is where you pay a small fee and you skip the line, and we feature you within 24 hours or less.',
    },
    {
      index: 16,
      question: 'Can you edit the price in the caption?',
      answer:
        'We can edit the price in the caption. Just send us an email with your request to submit@traded.co!',
    },
    {
      index: 17,
      question:
        'I am having issues submitting the deal through the form, what should I do?',
      answer:
        'Please email us at submit@traded.co or connect with us through our website chat box.',
    },
    {
      index: 18,
      question: 'How do I do a post collab with Traded?',
      answer:
        'On the submission form, simply choose the collaboration feature and write down the username you would like to post the transaction in collaboration.',
    },
    {
      index: 19,
      question: 'Can you add my older deals to your feed?',
      answer:
        'You can submit older deals through traded.co/submit. Bare in mind we charge $200 for deals that are older than 90 days.',
    },
    {
      index: 20,
      question: 'Can I submit a lease deal without the asking rent?',
      answer: 'We require the asking rent for all lease transactions.',
    },
    {
      index: 21,
      question: 'Why was my deal removed?',
      answer:
        'In some instances we remove posts when the landlord asked us to remove it, if you would like you can ask him for permission for us to unarchive the post. Also, if someone mentioned that the deal hasn’t closed yet. Lastly, if someone mentioned that the deal is incorrect and never happened. If your post was removed, please reach out to us at submit@traded.co or through our chat box.',
    },
    {
      index: 22,
      question: 'Can I post a for sale listing?',
      answer:
        'Please contact our ads team for more information about listings at ads@traded.co',
    },
    {
      index: 23,
      question:
        'I have two or more address that I want on the same post, is that possible?',
      answer:
        'Yes, the address needs to be bought or sold together and needs to be apart of a portfolio. Bare in mind we are only able to publish 10 addresses at a time. For larger portfolios, reach out to us at ads@traded.co',
    },
    {
      index: 24,
      question: 'Could I request where my headshot will be on the post?',
      answer:
        'Yes, please email submit@traded.co where you would like the headshot to be placed.',
    },
  ],
};

export const paymentQuestions = {
  data: [
    {
      index: 1,
      question: 'Why does it cost to submit a deal?',
      answer:
        'When we post a deal we need to craft and image, schedule it on social, tag relevant parties on all social media outlets, and post it on the website. Also, our prices have been standard for some time now.',
    },
    {
      index: 2,
      question:
        'I submitted a deal for free in the past, why do I have to pay now?',
      answer:
        'Our pricing strategy has changed over the years due to the large amount of submissions. Please note that we don’t charge to post on our Chicago, Texas, Boston, and New Jersey feeds.',
    },
    {
      index: 3,
      question: 'Is my submission refundable?',
      answer:
        'You may request a refund if your post has not yet been posted on Traded social media accounts.',
    },
    {
      index: 4,
      question: 'Can I pay with a credit card?',
      answer:
        'Yes. To pay with a credit card, simply select the “Stripe” option upon checkout at the bottom of the page. Stripe allows you to safely pay with a credit card. Stripe accepts Visa, Master Card, Amex, and Discover.',
    },
    {
      index: 5,
      question: 'How can I get a copy of my receipt?',
      answer:
        'You are automatically sent a copy of your receipt via the payment processor you chose. If you require and additional receipt or did not receive yours, please email us at submit@traded.co or reach out to us through our website chatbox.',
    },
    {
      index: 6,
      question: 'I am submitting a deal, but do not see the payment option?',
      answer:
        'The payment option should appear at the bottom of the page. If you do not see it, please refresh your browser or try using a different browser. We recommend using a desktop or laptop to submit the payment. If you continue to experice issues, please email us at submit@traded.co or reach out to us through our website chatbox.',
    },
    {
      index: 7,
      question: 'Why is there a fee to remove the post and repost?',
      answer:
        'When we post a deal we need to craft an image, schedule it on social, tag relevant parties on all social media outlets, and post it on the website. When we remove an image we need to remove everything, and then repost it.',
    },
  ],
};

export const agentProfileQuestions = {
  data: [
    {
      index: 1,
      question: 'What is a profile?',
      answer:
        'A profile is your personalized page that will feature your deals from the past and present.',
    },
    {
      index: 2,
      question: 'How do I edit my profile on the website?',
      answer:
        'Visit this link and fill out your profile edit request or email us at submit@traded.co. Our team will make edits within 24 hours or less: traded.co/profile-submissions/.',
    },
    {
      index: 3,
      question: 'How do I add older transactions to my profile?',
      answer:
        'Your profile will only features deals that have been published on our platform. We are in the midst of building a feature where you will be able to add your past deals.',
    },
    {
      index: 4,
      question:
        'I just posted a deal and I dont see the transaction on my profile?',
      answer:
        'Please be patient it could take up to 2-3 days to post your transaction on the website. If you submitted a deal that is not featured on your profile, please email us at submit@traded.co or reach out to us through our website chat.',
    },
    {
      index: 5,
      question: 'Can you update the stats on my profile?',
      answer:
        'The stats on the profiles are automatically updated based on the sum of the transaction deal amounts that any agent, agency, or lender has on their profile.',
    },
    {
      index: 6,
      question: 'Can you change my profile photo on my Agent Profile?',
      answer:
        'Please send us and email to submit@traded.co with all the posts that are missing on your profile, and we will get them up ASAP.',
    },
    {
      index: 7,
      question: 'Can you add my testimonial?',
      answer:
        'Please visit https://traded.co/submit-testimonial/ to add your testimonial.',
    },
    {
      index: 8,
      question: 'How do the stats work on the profile?',
      answer:
        'All profiles contain stats for deals that have been featured on traded. If you would like for new deals to start being featured, we would suggest submitting new deals as they happen on https://traded.co/submit.',
    },
    {
      index: 9,
      question: 'Do you have a list of buyers?',
      answer:
        'We do not provide lists of buyers. We advise you check the map section to search for recently traded sites and properties in your desired location. That may be a good indicator for you as to who is currently active in the market.',
    },
  ],
};
